Hey Kenny, how's it going, man?
Thanks for taking the time to do this.
Yeah, absolutely, man.
Um firstly,
can you just explain what made coming to
Carolina an attractive thing for you
while you were in free agency?
Yeah, I think
number one, I think coach Canales and
the track record he has with with
quarterbacks and and all the places he's
been and
you know, over the over his career, I've
watched a lot of tape. I've seen him at
different places.
Really like what he really like what he
does. I feel like it's been similar to
what I've done in college and what I did
in Philly.
So start off the bat, I think that that
was number one for me.
What specifically do you know about Dave
Canales and his history with
quarterbacks?
Yeah, so
I was just with Geno Smith over in Vegas
and Geno had nothing but great things to
say about him. So that was great, you
know, to to hear it from a player that
you know, worked with him.
You know, it was awesome. He was at my
pro day actually four years ago.
I grabbed lunch with him at at Fat Heads
down in South Side in Pittsburgh
and really just enjoyed my time with
him, you know, just a great person.
One of the guys that you really want to
be around in this in this league in this
profession. It's a tough business, but
you know, great people make it a lot
easier.
Yeah, so you know, just from a track
record standpoint, that's kind of as far
as we go back and then having Geno to
kind of ask questions to is great.
And final thing about Dave cuz those are
interesting answers.
Have you watched how he's kind of
brought this Carolina offense to life
over the past couple years as well?
Yeah, I have.
You know, my time in Philly they played
us, you know, right down to the wire,
you know, you know, in Philly and you
know, really like the things they were
doing.
Similar to what I felt like what we were
doing you know, with Kellen Moore and
and what we were doing in Philly. So I
thought it would be, you know, a really
good fit for me to play here.
Awesome, thanks. You got it.
David Newton followed by Jeff Hawkins.
Hey Kenny, David Newton with the
espn.com.
So
with Canales he's got like you said the
reputation for really developing
quarterbacks.
Um
have you given up at all on being a
starter? I mean, kind of where are you
on that right now? Is that just you feel
What do you feel like needs to be
developed to get you back to that level,
I guess is the question. Yeah, I just
really wanted to get in a great system
with with great people. I think that's
just where I'm at right now. Taking it a
day at a time, working really hard this
off season.
You know, just to improve my game in the
weight room, on the field.
Now that I finally, you know, got a
playbook and can watch some tape and
kind of dive into this this new system
is is really my main concern now.
So I'm really not trying to look, you
know, too far down the road. I want to
be a positive addition to this team
and help any way I can.
And what are your as far as Bryce goes,
what's your relationship with him? Have
y'all had one? I mean, you know, you're
only a class or two apart in in the
draft. So kind of tell me about that and
what's your impression of his journey so
far and some of the struggles he's had
and anything you can relate to.
Yeah, Bryce is a great guy. We go back
to the Heisman in 2021 was the first
time I met him.
You know, we had a joint practice
against Carolina when I was when I was
in Cleveland.
I was hurt so I really didn't get to do
too much, but I was able to, you know,
talk to him kind of there you know, at
the practice and and before the game.
You know, he's a great guy. Respect him
and his journey that he's been on.
You know, seems like he's constantly
working, constantly trying to improve
and seems like a great person.
So definitely looking forward to working
with him.
Thank you very much. Appreciate it.
Thank you.
Good afternoon and good luck this year.
Thank you. Along with the your
relationship
with Bryce, do you have any type of
a history with any of the anyone in the
in the receiver room or tight end room?
Um off the top of my head now, not in
the receiver.
Actually, you know what? I Smith, I
believe is is here. You know, I was with
him in Philly and and we got to work
together a lot.
Great guy, you know, really rooting for
him. It'll be awesome to see him in the
locker room again. He's got a great
personality.
So excited to work with him. I was
teammates actually with Pat Jones who's
on the defensive side at the University
of Pittsburgh
for four years and we you know, we
developed a really good friendship and I
know he's a big fisherman. So that's
something I hope we can we can do in the
spring together.
You're a fisherman, too? I am, yeah, a
little bit. Well, you have a few
opportunities around here. Perfect.
Um
what is your reflections on the bowl
game that you played at Bank of America
Stadium
and the play that resulted in the in the
rule change? Do you reflect on that at
all or or what
What is the your smile there?
What was that game like?
It's a great memory. That's why I'm
smiling. You know, that that was a
special night
you know, to do it in in Charlotte in
the ACC championship game and you know,
guys I played with for for five years. I
was a five-year guy and it's all we
talked about was winning the ACC
championship. So the fact that's my home
stadium now, I think it's pretty cool
and you know, hopefully we can make some
more great memories this season.
And that play?
Yeah, it was all just kind of, you know,
improv, I guess. Just just playing
playing football. They pulled up so far
away. I was going to go down and slide
and figured I'm not supposed to keep
going. So
it worked out well.
Hey, good luck this year.
Thank you.
Joe Person.
Kenny, congrats. Welcome to Charlotte.
Thank you. I am
wondering and David asked you this
variation of this question, but when you
see guys like Daniel Jones and and Malik
Willis, you know, kind of a a second
chapter in their career, so to speak, as
starters. Is that something and I know
you said that's not first and foremost
with you here, but is that something,
you know, you that you kind of look
forward to and hope you get a shot to to
write your own second chapter?
Yeah, of course. That's that's you know,
the the ultimate the ultimate goal.
But I think it's just, you know, things
happen in this league. You just keep
working cuz you never know when that
opportunity is going to come. You know,
I just want to be as prepared as I can
be.
You never know when that's going to
happen. I just want to put my best foot
forward.
Wanted to ask you, too. I'm I'm old
enough to remember
Matt Rhule and Scott Fitterer, you know,
coming to your pro day and really,
you know, evaluating you pretty,
you know, pretty seriously. What what
What do you remember about that
pre-draft where the Panthers were
concerned specifically?
Yeah, it was obviously a whole new um
staff and building and a lot of new
faces this time around, you know, coming
down here.
You know, but yeah, that whole draft
process is crazy. The the pro day,
everyone was there and I had a, you
know, pre-draft um visit down in
Charlotte. Got to see the city a little
bit more.
So from that standpoint, that's about
it. That that was kind of the same.
You know, I'm excited now that I'm here.
I can, you know, get around the city a
little bit more and you know, get to
know everybody in the building.
Thanks, Kenny. You got it.
Alex Zietlow.
Kenny, we asked you about Bryce, but
do you
do you know Andy Dalton at all in a
professional capacity? Do you remember
growing up watching him?
What's your I guess, like how do you
know Andy? Yeah, I I grew up watching
him, obviously, you know, just like a
lot of young quarterbacks coming up. Um
And then usually but before every game
that I've just about played Andy, you
know, we kind of catch up for 10 to 15
minutes just being in the, you know, the
quarterback
uh I guess like fraternity here in the
league that you just, you know, talk to
guys before the game.
You know, he's he's an awesome guy from
all of my experiences. So I'm definitely
excited to, you know, be in the room
with him and and learn as much as I can
from him.
And you'll you've been in
uh
offseason situations, training camp
situations where there've been
quarterback battles.
Uh how do you go about approaching that
sort of thing, particularly with
players that you've grown up admiring
and stuff like this?
Yeah, I think it's more of a a media fan
spectacle than it is a a player deal.
You know, regardless if you're in a
competition or not, you're showing up to
compete. You know, nothing really
changes
at least from my my my point of view.
Like I'm going in there every day to be
the best player I can be to try to
improve.
So that's the same if there is a
competition or if there isn't. You know,
so I don't think my life changes too
much.
Got it. Thanks. You got it, man. Thank
you.
Any more questions for Kenny?
All right, Kenny. Thanks so much for
taking the time to talk to us. Yeah,
appreciate you guys.
>> [music]
[music]